

## Mohammed Sinan Al-Mousa

Front-end developer



Erbil, Iraq

I am a front-end web developer I have worked on so many big projects and I Have solved problems inside react and 3rd party libraries, also I have 2 years Of working experience with "Optimiza", I built a dashboard and it works as a CMS for their projects, today I can build any complex front-end app using React ecosystem or any framework with a lot of features.





https://mohammed-sinan.netlify.app/

## **Work Experience**

July 2021 - Present

### Front-end developer

OPTIMIZA.ca

In this company, I worked on a lot of projects. The biggest one was building a dashboard and developing it. We were using this dashboard as a CMS for our projects. In this project, we used these technologies (umi js , dva js, and antd)

January 2021

#### Dashboard with react

This is my biggest project so far. I used React as a base and reactrouter for routing and redux for data management. This dashboard will offers (a smart layout system, reducers injectors, and a smart Routing system ) All of these features are automated importers that you can define once and for all.

October 2019 - September 2020

#### Javascript, APIs, and React

At this time I learned a lot of advanced things like (oop, APIs, Functional programming, and routes). I have several projects that reflect my progress on my GitHub.

For example (webpack-starter, combine express with react, and the Solution for React Router)

February 2018 - October 2019

### **Website Clones**

I build a lot of website clones with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. At this time I wasn't that good at UX/UI. That's why I built website clones as a sample (antd-webpage, tracker, and greener) and I learned from this a lot of things (responsive design, animations, HTML SOE, virtual dom in javascript, and. layouts)

#### Skills

- HTML 5
- CSS 3
- JavaScript
- · React.js
- Redux
- APIs
- · Sass/Less
- Bootstrap
- Ant Design

## Languages

- English Intermediate
- · Arabic Native or Bilingual

- Webpack
- GraphQL
- NextJS
- TypeScript

# Education



# University of Tikrit

**Business administration** 

Powered by CakeResume